[bells chiming]
NETFLIX 原创剧集
你好
[Joe] Well, hello there.
你是谁？
Who are you?
看你的样子是个学生
Based on your vibe, a student.
你穿着宽松的衬衫
Your blouse is loose.
你不是来引人注意的 但那些手镯叮当作响
You're not here to be ogled, but those bracelets, they jangle.
你想要些许关注
You like a little attention.
好吧 你引起了我的兴趣
Okay, I bite.
你在找书 找小说 首字母从“F”到“K”
You search the books. Fiction, "F" through "K."
好了…
Now...
你不是那种标准的找福克纳的书 却永远读不到最后的没安全感的女生
Hmm, you're not the standard insecure nymph
hunting for Faulkner you'll never finish.
健康的肤色说明 你也不读斯蒂芬金的书
Too sun-kissed for Stephen King.
你会买谁的书呢？
Who will you buy?
对不起
[Beck gasps] Sorry.
你听上去很抱歉 好像你为当一个好姑娘而尴尬
[Joe] You sound apologetic, like you're embarrassed to be a good girl,
你低声对我说了第一个词
and you murmur your first word to me.
你好
Hello.
你在这里工作吗？
Do you work here?
没错
Guilty.
-你要找什么吗？ -宝拉福克斯的书
-Can I help you find something? -Paula Fox.
挺有眼光
It's a good choice.
被你这么肯定 感觉有点怪
Hmm, I feel weirdly validated.
[chuckles] Follow me.
跟我来吧
（知名作家）
她的书在这里
She's gonna be in here.
“知名作家”？ 我以为福克斯没什么名气呢
"Celebrity authors"? I thought Fox was pretty obscure.
她是科特妮洛芙的外婆
She is Courtney Love's maternal grandmother.
你应该不知道
You're not expected to know that.
很好 我不知道
Good. I didn't.
穆尼先生想把哪怕只有一点出名的 作者的书都放在这里
Mr. Mooney wants anyone in here who's even tangentially famous.
他觉得这样能卖出更多的书
He thinks it sells more books.
真可悲
That's sad.
人们看什么书流行就买什么书
People buying books because of what's popular,
而不是因为他们想在某些方面 被感动或是被改变
and not because they wanna be moved or changed in some way.
对 是有这种风气
Yeah. It's an epidemic.
嗯 你看到这家伙了吗？ 这个 你身后戴眼镜的这个
Yeah, you see this guy? Here, the glasses, behind you.
他刚刚进来时拿了丹布朗最新的小说
He just grabbed Dan Brown's latest on the way in.
所以他会再转上五或十分钟
So he's gonna wander around for another, like, five or ten minutes,
去找一本能装装样子的书一并买下
just to find something legitimate to buy with it.
就像那些买麦片的人 其实是去买安全套的
Oh, like the cereal guys buy when they're really there for condoms.
那只会更明显 还不如敢做敢当
Only makes it more conspicuous. Like, own your shit.
如果丹布朗就是你的心头爱 就坦荡承认吧
If Dan Brown's your kink, then be out about it.
最后 人们真让人失望 对吗？
[scoffs] At the end of the day,
people really are disappointing, aren't they?
有时候他们会让你惊讶
Sometimes they surprise you.
-宝拉福克斯 在最顶层 需要我… -不 我能够到
-Paula Fox. Top shelf. You want me to... -Oh, no, I got it.
你没穿胸罩吗？
[Joe] Oh. Are you not wearing a bra?
你想让我注意到
And you want me to notice.
如果是在拍电影
If this was a movie,
我会一把抓住你 然后我们会在书堆里做爱
I'd grab you and we'd go at it right in the stacks.
你读过她的小说吗？ 《绝望的人们》 那是她最棒的作品
Have you read her fiction? Desperate Characters, it's her best.
我一直听说那本书
[sighs] That's what I keep hearing.
-你没读过《绝望的人们》？ -我知道
-You haven't read Desperate Characters? -I know. I know.
我担心那书名不符实
I'm worried it's not gonna live up to the hype.
我可以打保票那书跟大家说的一样好
I can safely say it is that good.
这真是很高的认可 虽然是书店工作人员口中说出来的
That's a high endorsement. And from a bookstore clerk, nonetheless.
是书店经理
Well, it's bookstore manager.
喂？这里有工作人员吗？
Hello? Anyone working here?
混蛋
-Asshole. -Mmm...
-Whoa. -[chuckles]
能快点吗？我很着急
Do you mind? Uh, I'm in a hurry.
他很生气要买本塞林格的书 让自己觉得被尊重
[Joe] He's just pissed he's gotta buy Salinger to feel respectable
而其实他真正想做的是吃奇多 在苹果设备上看黄片手淫
when all he really wants to do is eat Cheetos and jerk it to iPorn
然后再读完丹布朗的书
before washing it all down with a Dan Brown chaser.
祝您今天愉快 先生
Have a nice day, sir.
好了 我决定买这本
Okay, I'm going for it.
-好极了 你不会后悔的 -最好不会
-Good. You won't regret it. -I'd better not.
宝拉福克斯 不错
Paula Fox. Nice.
她是科特妮洛芙的外婆
You know, she was, uh, Courtney Love's maternal grandmother.
所以我才买的
That's why I'm buying it.
你有足够的现金付账 但你想让我知道你的名字
[Joe] You have enough cash to cover this, but you want me to know your name.
-“吉娜薇”？ -是的
-"Guinevere"? -Yeah.
我父母太不会取名了
My parents were assholes with the whole naming thing.
但大家都叫我贝可
But everyone just calls me Beck.
你叫乔伊…
And you're Joe...
戈登伯格
Goldberg.
大家都叫我乔伊
Everyone calls me Joe.
[chuckles]
你不祝我今天愉快吗？
Aren't you gonna tell me to have a nice day?
祝你今天愉快 贝可
You have a nice day, Beck.
也祝你今天愉快 乔伊
You have one yourself, Joe.
你对我微笑 为我说的笑话发笑
[Joe] You smiled, laughed at my jokes,
告诉了我你的名字 问了我的名字
told me your name, asked for mine.
她在上面写她的号码了吗？ 她对你有意思
She write her number on there? She was on you hard.
不 她只是很友好
No, she was just being nice.
我会立刻去谷歌上搜索她的全部信息
I'd be googling the hell out of her right now.
你知道她的全名了
You know her full name.
那也太积极了 伊森
That's pretty aggressive, Ethan.
我怎么跟你说的？一定要主动出击
What do I tell you? Always be closing that shit.
你需要我的话 我就在烹饪书那一块
[both] If you need me, I'll be in cookbooks.
但我是去工作 不是去玩的 我发誓
But for work. Not for fun. I swear.
最后 人们真让人失望 对吗？
[Joe] At the end of the day, people are really just disappointing, aren't they?
但你是吗 贝可？你是吗？
But are you, Beck? Are you?
是 人们寻找“命中注定的那个人”
Yes, people find "the one."
我相信 我努力做到思想开明
I believe that. I try to stay open.
我也曾恋爱过 她让我心碎了 贝可
I was in love once. She broke my heart, Beck.
她真的伤透了我的心
Ugh, she really did a number on me.
我应该看到那些迹象的
I should've seen the signs.
但我们在恋爱的时候永远看不到
But we never do when we're in love.
例子一 克劳迪亚跟罗恩
-Exhibit A. Claudia and Ron. -[indistinct arguing]
我出去喝了几杯 别追问了
[Ron] I went out for a couple of drinks. Get off my back.
克劳迪亚是个护士 单身母亲
[Joe] Claudia's a nurse. Single parent.
别烦我！你在打电话…
[Claudia] Leave me alone! You're on your phone...
你觉得她恋爱的时候 知道罗恩是个混蛋吗？
[Joe] You think she knew Ron was a shitbag when she fell in love?
不 她那时觉得他是个王子
No, she thought he was a prince.
嘿 帕克
Hey, Paco.
你好吗 乔伊？
'Sup, Joe?
现在
[Joe] And now,
-她毁掉的不仅是自己的人生 -别烦我！
-hers is not the only life she ruined. -[Claudia] Leave me alone!
为什么回家这么让你心烦？
Why is coming home such a chore for you? [continues indistinctly]
没事吧？
Is everything cool in there?
-没事 妈妈和罗恩只是在说话 -你总是跟你的朋友出去鬼混！
Yeah, Mom and Ron are just talking.
-我受够了！ -哇噢
[Claudia] You always go out with your friends!
-And I'm sick of it! -Wow.
那本书你快看完了 是吗？
You are burning through that book, aren't you?
我读得很快 很好看
Reads quick. It's good.
（《三剑客》）
Let me know when you finish. I'll get you another one.
你读完了告诉我 我再拿一本给你
去你的 罗恩！滚出去！别烦我
[Claudia] Screw you, Ron! Get out of here! Leave me alone.
[continues indistinctly]
你饿吗？
Are you hungry?
因为我买了这个肉丸三明治
'Cause, you know, I just got this meatball sub,
但我想到还有些昨晚剩下的泰国菜
but I remembered I have Thai from last night.
不了 我妈妈晚点会给我做饭的
Nah. My mom will just make me something later.
真可惜 这个不能放 要被扔掉了
That's a shame. This won't keep. It's getting tossed.
你确定吗 乔伊？
You sure, Joe?
“人人为我 我为人人”
"All for one and one for all."
问题是 贝可…爱是很微妙的
[Joe] The point, Beck... Love is, uh, tricky.
[rock song playing on record]
（穆尼书店）
人需要保护自己
[Joe] A guy needs to protect himself.
我得确定你是个安全的人
I had to be sure you're safe.
从你的名字开始是最好的
And your name was a glorious place to start.
没多少人叫吉娜薇贝可
Not a lot of Guinevere Becks.
找到你了 所有的账号都对公众可见
And there you were. Every account set to public.
你想要被看见、被听见、被人了解
You want to be seen, heard, known.
当然 我照做了
Of course, I obliged.
出生并成长于南塔克特岛
Born and raised, Nantucket Island.
有个兄弟叫克莱德 一个姐妹叫安雅
A brother, Clyde, and sister, Anya.
你的父母真是不会取名
Your parents really were assholes about the names.
你12岁的时候父母离异 你的父亲从此了无音讯
Your folks split when you were 12. Your dad dropped out of the picture.
你上了布朗大学 专业是文学 酷
Went to Brown where you majored in lit. Cool.
辅修人渣课程
And minored in douchebags. Hmm.
然后去了纽约市攻读艺术硕士 大概想要成就一番名气吧
And then on to NYC to conquer an MFA and make your mark, presumably.
你现在还在写作 写得很少
Now you still write. Barely.
太忙碌于过你五年之后 都不会记得的生活了
Too busy living out moments you won't remember five years from now.
我知道 因为你一直 在发布这种生活的点滴
I know this because you post about this life all the goddamn time.
[all speaking indistinctly]
老实说 这是你最没吸引力的部分了 贝可
[Joe] Candidly, it's the least appealing thing about you, Beck.
你在我们相遇几小时后发布了这个
You posted this hours after our encounter.
[camera shutter clicks]
没有提到书店里 那个可爱的家伙 让我担心
[Joe] I was concerned you didn't mention that cute guy in a bookstore.
然后我意识到你的网上人生并不真实
And then I realized your online life isn't real.
这是个…拼贴画
It's a collage.
你拼贴出了这个贝可的生活 这个…
You paste this Beck up. This...
自信、讨喜、可爱、柔韧的小可人
together, lovable, cute, bendy little creature.
如果有什么的话 你没有把我 分享给你的订阅者这件事
If anything, the fact that you didn't share me with your followers
只证实了我们真的有联系
only confirms we really connected.
接着我在网上找到了你的地址
The next thing our little friend the Internet gave me was your address.
（街景-班克街171号）
就是这里 有着无遮挡的大窗户
There it is, with its big, naked windows.
挺好 太好了
It's nice. Too nice.
我想这是拿补贴的校舍
I'm thinking subsidized school housing.
天啊！你好像从来没看过恐怖电影 或是新闻
Jesus! It's like you've never seen a horror movie or the news.
但你想让人们看你 不是吗？
But you want people to watch, don't you?
我计划等我们熟悉之后
You know, I plan on asking you about this quality
问问关于你这项特质的问题
when we get to know each other better.
一个提议
A proposal.
不如我们明天一起共度吧？
Why don't we spend the day together tomorrow?
只有你跟我？
Just you and me?
[Beck] To everyone out there chasing their dreams, don't give up.
“写给那些追逐梦想的人 别放弃”
“同时 享受芝士通心粉吧！”
And in the meantime, mac and cheese!
很可爱 没深度 但可爱 你还有更多面吗？让我们发现一下吧
[Joe] It's cute. Not deep. But cute. Is there more to you? Let's find out.
天一破晓 我们的一天就开始了
Our day starts at the ass-crack of dawn.
我从你发布的日程表了解到 你6点半要去教一堂
I know from your posted schedule that you teach a 6:30 class
被称为“起来运动”的课
called Get Up N Flow.
你温柔地触碰那些来自苏荷区 双眼无神的肥胖妈妈们汗湿的背部…
You caress the sweaty backs of bulimic, dead-eyed real mommies of SoHo...
我喜欢你今天的线条 塔莎
I am loving your form today, Tasha.
…微笑着说着客套的鼓励的话
[Joe] ...offering smiles and lies of encouragement.
[Beck continues indistinctly]
到了10点 你在大学的 浪漫主义课程上当助教
[Joe] By 10:00, you're at campus to TA a Romantics class
给某个教授当助手
and play Vanna White to some shirt.
早上好 莱西教授
Morning, Professor Leahy.
我跟你说过了叫我保罗 你准备好上课了吗？
I told you, it's Paul. Are you ready for class?
教授显然想上你
[Joe] Professor Obvious wants to fuck you.
你很聪明 你让他以为 有一天他会有机会
Now, you're smart. You let him think one day he might.
这样又有什么损失呢 对吧？
And what's the harm in that, right?
下课后 你去你最喜欢的咖啡馆
After class, you head to your favorite café
进行一整天第一次的写作
to write for the first time all day.
但你的生活并不如你所愿
But your life doesn't cooperate.
你有钱的女友们才刚睡醒
Your wealthy girlfriends have just now woken up,
除了策划下一个
and have nothing better to do
可以在社交软件上发布的无聊夜生活 就没有什么好做的了
than plan their next pointless yet instagrammable night.
我们能现实一点吗？
Can we get real for a second?
你交友的品味有问题 贝可
You have questionable taste in friends, Beck.
-干杯！ -耶！
-[all] Cheers! -Yeah!
-对了 生日快乐！ -太感谢了
-Oh, yes. Happy birthday! -[Annika laughs] Thank you so much.
生活中买的东西太昂贵了
[Joe] And expensive taste in lives.
-准备好了吗？ -谢谢
-Ready? -Thank you.
你喜欢吗？
-[gasps] -Do you like it?
不 我不喜欢 我当然喜欢了！
No, I hate it. Of course I love it!
杰森都不给她买那么好的内衣
Jason didn't even get her something that nice,
安妮卡最后就让他爆菊了
and Annika finally let him do anal.
-我的天！ -拜托 那是时候到了
-[Lynn] Oh, my God! -Please, please, it was time.
接下来请打开我的礼物 告诉我你有多讨厌我 姑娘
Please open my gift next and tell me how much you hate me then, lady.
[Annika gasps]
一只蝴蝶？ 这是我的年度灵兽 你记得？
A butterfly? It's my spirit animal for the year. You remembered?
只是因为你一直喋喋不休地提到它
Only 'cause you wouldn't shut up about it.
你非常想要融入她们
[Joe] You want so badly to be one of them.
-生日快乐 -你看起来真漂亮
-[Beck] Happy birthday. -[Annika] You look so beautiful.
她们之后就无事可做了
[Joe] Well, they've got nothing to do after this.
对 她们会开派对直到凌晨5点 然后明天再一起聚会
So, yeah, they'll party till 5:00 and scrape it together tomorrow.
但你不行 你得要为谋生而工作
But you can't. You have to work for a living.
麦昆牌的 贝可？多少钱？
A McQueen, Beck? How much was it?
是清仓商品
[chuckles] It was on clearance.
麦昆2010年上吊后
They haven't put a McQueen scarf on clearance
围巾就没有清仓出售过了
since he hung himself in 2010.
就算她值得也太贵了
It'd be too much even if she did deserve it,
何况她不值得
which she does not.
你的朋友并不全是笨蛋
[Joe] Hmm. Not all your friends are dumb.
你总是这样
[Peach] You always do this.
你大手笔地买 你买不起的东西 因为…
You make, like, a big gesture that you can't afford because...
-抱歉 你人太好了 -没什么大不了的 我有礼品卡
-[scoffs] I'm sorry, you're too nice. -It's no big deal. I had, um, a gift card.
你有多缺钱？
How broke are you?
告诉我怎么回事
Just tell me what's up.
听上去她其实很在乎你
[Joe] Actually sounds like she cares.
听着 我很感激…
[Beck] Look, I appreciate--
你为什么不让我借你点现金呢？
[Peach] Why don't you just let me loan you some cash?
好吗？我一直跟你说 这没什么
Okay? I keep telling you, it's nothing.
同时 听上去还很居高临下
[Joe] Also, sounds condescending.
你知道我愿意为你做一切事情 别忘记了
You know I'd do anything for you. Don't forget that.
-确定不跟我们出去玩吗？ -我得写作
-Sure you can't come out with us? -I gotta write.
好姑娘 晚点聊吧？
Virtuous. Catch you later?
那是你最好的朋友了吗？
[Joe] Is that the best friend you've got?
如果是的话 贝可 你真的很孤独
If so, Beck, you really are alone.
你的社交媒体编造出了一个谎言
Your social media's a liar.
你在上面表现成 一个逍遥自在的业余文学爱好者
It says you're a happy-go-lucky dilettante.
但在一切表象之下 你似乎是有真材实料的
But, underneath it all, you seem like the genuine article.
注意力缺失 当然 但一旦关上门…
Stretched ADD thin, sure, but as soon as the door closes...
你又回到了键盘前 想要努力写作
you're back at the keyboard, trying to write.
[cell phone vibrates]
[sighs]
谢谢
[man] Thanks.
不用找了 伙计
Keep the change, man.
嘿 让我上去
Hey. Let me up.
贝可 这人到底是谁？
[Joe] Uh, Beck, who the fuck is this?
我最好的朋友看到 你在我带你去的派对上
My best friend walked in on you getting your dick sucked
在洗手间里 让一个陌生女人帮你口交！
by some random woman in a bathroom at a party that I took you to!
我喝醉了 我都没射精
I was wasted. I didn't even finish.
你就这么道歉？“我没到高潮” 那是你要说的话吗？
That's your apology? "I didn't cum." That's the one you're going with?
我显然不应该跟除你之外的
I obviously shouldn't have gone in the bathroom
任何女孩去洗手间
with any girl that wasn't you.
但她说她有上好的可卡因 我压力一直非常大
But she said she had good coke, and I'd been seriously stressed.
我跟乔诺开始做这行时
I thought, when Johno and I started our line,
我以为就会是挑选一下口味之类的
it was gonna be like picking out flavors and shit.
结果是16个小时 关于微生物管理的演讲
It turns out it's 16-hour lectures on microbial management.
那就是为什么没有人 开自己的手工汽水公司
And that's why no one starts their own artisanal soda company,
还有为什么美国人 一直得喝让自己得癌症的垃圾
and why America has to keep drinking crap that's giving 'em cancer.
你竟然把你的口交外遇 跟治愈癌症联系起来了
You actually managed to connect your illicit blowjob to curing cancer.
真是了不起
I'm genuinely impressed.
贝可 我…
Beck, I...
讲真的 我现在工作很忙
Seriously, I am drowning in work.
我没时间一直跟你乱搞 或是做什么你擅长的事
I don't have time to keep hooking up or whatever it is you're even capable of.
我知道我做了些蠢事 但我现在改了
I know I've done some stupid shit, but I'm on it now.
我不想只跟你上床而已
I don't wanna be just some guy you sleep with.
天啊 你让我疯狂了
[whispering] God, you make me insane.
厉害了 贝可 看上去真是个理想对象
[Joe] Way to go, Beck. Looks like a catch.
本杰明J阿什比三世 有三个同名的
Benjamin J. Ashby III. Oh, there's three of them.
出生在格林威治 上的是寄宿学校
Greenwich-born, boarding-school bred.
他的爸爸是阿什比经纪行的本阿什比
His father is the Ben Ashby of Ashby Brokerage.
做过两份失败的工作 模特 天啊
Two failed careers. Model. Oh, boy.
还有一个约会软件的联合创始人
And co-creator of a dating app
是一个通过音乐品味把人 关联起来的软件 叫做“恋爱交友”
that connects people through musical tastes called LoveHooks.
现在是手工饮料家庭汽水的 首席执行官
Current CEO of Home Soda Artisanal Beverages.
座右铭…
Motto...
“用手喝更好” 这话毫无意义
"Drink better by hand," which makes no sense,
但放在一个穿着价值六百美元
but evokes a homespun quality
日本运动鞋的家伙身上 有种朴素的感觉
that lines up with a guy who wears $600 Japanese sneakers.
发型、他想要通过转发“黑人的命 也是命”的推文隐藏的特权
The hair, the privilege he tries to hide with retweets of Black Lives Matter.
不想听上去像是批判别人 但这家伙就跟美国精神完全格格不入
Not to sound judgey, but this guy is everything wrong with America.
所以我要调查
See, this is why I do my research.
你爱上了错的人
You fall for the wrong men.
坏男人们
Bad men.
你让他们进你家 你让他们伤害你
You let them in. You let them hurt you.
还不能确定 但我猜
Too far away to know for sure, but my guess is,
要是他有一点可能让你高潮
if he came anywhere close to making you cum,
你就会做出百老汇水平的表演
you would've made a Broadway show out of it.
但你没有 因为他没那能耐
But you didn't, 'cause he didn't.
[exhales]
（《绝望的人们》 小说 宝拉福克斯著）
-《绝望的人们》 -是的 我刚买的
-"Desperate Characters." -Yeah, I just got it.
我读完了可以借给你 这应该是她写得最好的一部
Borrow it when I'm done. It's supposed to be her best.
我们请的乔诺的顾问
Johno's consultant we brought in,
她一直在跟我说这种东西
she's been all over me about this kind of thing.
烧些东西让办公室充满正能量
Saged the crap out of the office.
书名里有“绝望”两字
The book title has the word "desperate" in it.
但你别觉得自己是个绝望的人 贝可
You don't want to think of yourself as a desperate character, Beck.
因为你正相反 宝贝
Because you're the opposite, babe.
你是我认识最聪明的姑娘
You're the smartest girl I know.
老实说 我为你着迷
Honestly, you blow me away.
[cell phone vibrating]
该死 该走了 乔诺一直在给我打电话
Oh, shit. Gotta roll. Johno's blowing up my phone.
嘿 你应该来办公室试尝一些新口味
Hey, you should come by the office, test out some new flavors.
我们开发出了孜然口味 我知道你有多喜欢印度菜
We're doing cumin. I know how much you like Indian food.
当然好 听上去很好
Sure. Sounds good.
另外 你胖了点
It looks good on you, by the way.
看上去不错
The extra weight.
对 嘿 我来了 兄弟
Yeah. Hey. I'm on my way, bro.
你们点了批萨？
You guys ordering pizzas?
对 别像上次那样坑我了 要不含麸质的脆皮
Yeah, don't dick me over like last time. Gluten-free crust.
别从那家素食店订 素食芝士吃起来跟屎一样
Not from that vegan place. Vegan cheese tastes like asshole.
[door opens and closes]
我说的是法国美食
[door closes]
[Benji] I'm talking French gourmet shit.
不 乔诺 听我说
No. Johno. Johno. Listen to me.
他们做不了一半不含麸质的 因为那是生面团
They can't do half-gluten-free 'cause it's dough.
他们得用斯佩尔特小麦粉做的面团
They have to use a spelt dough.
所以你还没满足
[Joe] So you didn't finish.
[breathing heavily]
[gasps]
就这样
Just like that.
谢谢 你真好
Thank you. You're so kind. [chuckles]
你能帮我叫辆出租车吗？
I don't suppose you can help me get a cab, can you?
当然可以
Of course.
-谢谢 -嗯
-Thanks. -Yeah.
[Claudia moaning]
哇噢 别告诉我说你已经读完了
Wow. Don't tell me you're finished already.
差不多了
Almost.
太好看了
It's so good.
但有时候对话很奇怪
Sometimes the dialogue's weird, though.
像是他们要杀掉彼此的时候 还很客气
Like when they're killing each other and still all nice about it.
那是19世纪 人们还是很礼貌的
Well, it was the 19th century. People still had manners.
我希望我们能去再拿一本
I was hoping we could go get another one.
已经很晚了 帕克 我不知道
[sighs] I mean, it's pretty late, Pac. I don't know.
[Claudia moaning] Oh, yeah.
是啊
我想让你高潮…
I want you to cum...
今晚很有气氛 贝可 因为除了我之外的所有人都在做爱
[Joe] Something's in the air tonight, Beck,
'cause everyone but me is getting action.
就连爱情鸟都在交配
Even the lovebirds made up.
嗯 为什么不去呢？当然要去了
Yeah. Yeah, why not? Sure.
你知道仲马是个黑人吗？ 我上谷歌搜索他了
[Paco] Did you know Dumas was a black dude? I googled him.
他的祖母是个奴隶 他的父亲是个准将
His grandmother was a slave, and his dad was a brigadier general.
他杀了半个营的人
He killed like half a battalion.
你在书店工作 可能已经知道了
You probably knew that since you work at a bookstore.
我不知道
I didn't.
-你怎么会在这里工作呢？ -在我比你大一点的年纪时
-How'd you get to work here, anyway? -Mr. Mooney gave me a job
穆尼先生给了我这份工作 他像是收留了我
when I was just a little older than you. He sort of took me in.
-他似乎是个好人 -他是个混蛋
-He seems nice. -He's a dick.
但他爱书 他也教会了我爱书
But he loved books, and he taught me to love them, too.
我从没见他来过这里
I never see him around here.
-他死了吗？ -不 他只是老了
-Is he dead? -No. He's just old.
对不起 帕克
I'm sorry, Pac.
我留了一本给你的 但伊森一定卖掉了
I had one back here for you, but Ethan must've sold it.
-卖了什么？ -你下一本要读的书
-Sold what? -Your next read.
来吧 我让你看看我们放好书的地方
Come on. I'll show you where we keep the good stuff.
真奇特
[Paco] Freaky.
这是个笼子
It's the Cage.
是我们放早期版本跟收藏的地方
It's where we keep early editions and collectibles.
很冷
It's cold.
18度 用于保存书籍的
Sixty-five degrees. For the books.
要是僵尸来了 我要藏在这里
If the zombies come, this is where I'm hiding.
不如把那杯奶昔放下吧？
Why don't you set that milkshake down?
小心 约瑟夫
[Mooney] Careful, Joseph.
书的价值完全在于其保存状态 我来告诉你
When it comes to the value of a book, it's all about condition. I'll show you.
温度一直是18度
[Joe] It's always 65 degrees.
40%的湿度 太潮的话 书页会发霉…
Humidity 40%. Too moist, the pages can mildew...
太干的话就会变脆
[Mooney] Too dry, they get brittle.
一直要让书直立
Always keep books upright
书脊就不会卷起来或是变弯 或是我们说的“翘起来”
so the spines don't become rolled or warped or what we call "cocked."
永远不要折书页
And we never wanna fold or crease the pages.
用不含化学成分的抹布 拂去封面的灰尘
And we dust the covers with a chemical-free duster.
拿的时候一直拿书脊柱
Always towards the spine.
这间屋子里不能进阳光
Under no circumstances is there any sunlight in this room.
阳光会像火一样快地把书给毁掉
Sunlight can ruin a book as fast as fire.
比火更快
Faster.
为了保存好一些老书 要记的东西真多
That's a lot of stuff to remember just to take care of some old books.
生活中最有价值的东西通常是…
The most valuable things in life are usually...
最无助的
the most helpless.
所以需要像我们一样的人 去保护它们 知道吗？
So they need people like us to protect them. You know?
“堂肯德鸡”
"Don Quicks-oat."
是吉诃德 说的是一个信奉骑士精神的人
Quixote. It's about a guy who believes in chivalry,
他决定当一个老派的骑士
so he decides to be an old-school knight.
什么是骑士精神？
What's chivalry?
是用尊敬的态度对待别人 特别是女人 像男人们应该做的那样
It's treating people with respect. Especially women. Like men should.
是本好书 是我最爱的书之一
It's good. It's one of my favorites.
我可能不应该拿这本回家
I probably shouldn't take this home.
这不是第一版 只是旧版
It's not a first edition, it's just an old one.
再说了 我信任你
Besides, I trust you.
-你去哪了 帕克？ -我们只是去买奶昔了
-Where you been, Paco? -We just grabbed some milkshakes.
-你刚跟陌生人走了？ -乔伊不是陌生人
-You just walk off with strangers? -Joe's not a stranger.
是 他是
Yes, he is.
快进去 好吗？
Inside. Now. Okay?
离我女朋友的孩子远点
Keep away from my girlfriend's kid.
对不起 但他刚刚在外面 让他听到你们在里面的动静不大好吧
Look, I'm sorry, but he was out here, and he could hear everything in there.
别教我怎么养育孩子
Don't you tell me how to parent.
这套装好人的行为 在其他人身上可能管用
This whole nice guy act might work on other people.
我当假释官当了15年 我能看出你是什么货色
I'm a parole officer, 15 years, and I can see what you are.
你是个打女人的酒鬼
[Joe] Well, you're an alcoholic shitbag who beats women.
所以拜托来开导我吧
So, please, enlighten me.
你是个怪胎
You're a freak.
离帕克远点 不然的话
So, stay away from Paco, because if you don't,
我会拿把牛排刀把你的眼睛挖出来
I'll grab a steak knife and I'll cut those freak eyes out.
世界上有可怕的人 贝可
[Joe] There are scary people in the world, Beck.
所以保证安全很重要
That's why it's important to be safe.
以及为什么我要做我将要做的事
And why I have to do what I'm about to do.
有趣的事情
Fun fact.
你知道法律要求要调查煤气泄漏吗？
Did you know the law requires gas leaks to be investigated?
我见到你之后学到了很多
I've been learning a lot since I met you.
嘿 贝可？你又没关门
Hey, Beck? You left the door open again.
我以为我们说好了 不会再发生这种事了
I thought we said we weren't gonna do that anymore.
我很小心地在你一整天都有事的时候 打给了煤气公司
I was careful to call the gas company on a day when you had a full schedule.
我不想吓到你
I wouldn't wanna scare you.
嘿 贝可在家吗？
Hey. Is Beck here?
不在 管理员让我进来的 有人说这里有煤气泄漏
Nope. Super let me in. Someone reported a leak.
对 嗯 她提到过 没事吧？
Right. Yeah. She mentioned that. Is everything okay?
对 没问题 告诉你女朋友没有泄漏
Yeah, all clear. Tell your girlfriend there's no leak.
我弄完了 所以…
I'm done, so...
好的 谢谢 我来锁门
Okay. Thanks. Well, I can just lock up.
我只是需要知道你到底是什么样的人
I just need to know who you really are.
除了是一个住在
Besides a broke poetry student
你永远租不起的校舍里 写诗的穷学生外
in a subsidized apartment you could never afford.
在哪里 贝可？
Where is it, Beck?
我们住在一起后 你家就不会像个猪窝了
When we live together, your place won't be a pigsty.
我可以打扫
I'll clean for us.
你不会吃这些速冻垃圾食品了 我每天都会为你下厨 我保证
And you won't eat all this frozen shit. I'll cook for you every day. I promise.
我甚至会帮你洗衣服
I'll even do your laundry.
呵护你最爱的书
And take care of your favorite books.
我每天早上都会整理床单
I'll make our bed every morning.
在这里
Oh, there it is.
不管你多抗拒我
And no matter how hard you fight me,
我都永远会确保 你的密码能保护你的电脑
I will always make sure you password protect your devices.
“一天 你将不再需要爱
[Leahy] "One day You won't need love anymore
一天 你将不再在这世界上行走
One day, you won't walk through the world
好像让一切停下是你的工作
As though it was your job To hold everything up
太阳、天空 黑夜里最难的部分”
The sun, the sky The hard part of the night"
很棒
It's good.
非常棒
It's quite good.
但是贝可 其它的呢？ 你还欠我20页
But, Beck, where's the rest? You owe me 20 more pages.
[sighs] I've been, honestly, working every day, and grading papers--
老实说 我每天都在工作 给论文打分…
如果时间安排不过来 就做回兼职生吧
If the schedule is too rigorous, drop back to part-time.
那我就不够资格当助教了
But then I won't qualify to TA.
我需要现金付房租 我会无家可归的
I need the cash. The housing. I'd lose my place.
你会搞定的 你很聪明 不然你就不会到这里来了
You'll figure it out. You're smart, or you wouldn't be here.
-拜托 莱西教授… -叫我保罗
-Please, Professor Leahy-- -Paul.
保罗 我会在这周结束前 把文稿给您的
Paul. I'll get you the pages by the end of the week.
我不能做兼职 好吗？
I can't go to part-time, okay?
我对你期待很高
[sighs] I'm rooting for you.
你需要加把劲
You just need to keep up.
很乐意跟你进一步讨论一下 找一天放学之后的晚上
Happy to discuss further. After class some evening.
如果我们要认真讨论诗歌 就应该边喝边聊
If we're gonna seriously discuss poetry, it should be over a drink.
有一家我很喜欢的美食酒吧…
There's a little gastropub I love...
我很愿意去 保罗
I would love that, Paul. [chuckles]
只是 你的妻子会有什么感觉…
Just, uh, how would your wife feel about you--
关于我帮助一个有抱负的作家吗？ 她很明白 我一向这么慷慨
About me helping out an aspiring writer? She's used to my generosity.
[chuckles]
那就周四晚上吧？
[Leahy] So, Thursday night, then?
就周四晚上吧
Thursday night it is.
好极了
Excellent.
别为接下来几天担心 回家准备吧
And don't worry about the next few days. Just go home and get caught up.
“今晚需要见你”
[Beck] Need to see you tonight.
“如果可以的话 宝贝 我会工作到很晚”
[Benji] Will if I can, babe. Working late.
“另外 我还是能在手指上 闻到你的味道”
P.S., I can still smell you on my fingers.
通过彻底查看你的电脑 我知道了两样决定性的事情
[Joe] I learned two definitive things by scouring your computer.
首先 没有看到你父亲的近照 因为他死了
First, there are no recent pictures of your dad because he's dead.
他吸毒过量 是你发现了他的尸体
He OD'd and you were the one that found him.
你开始写了几首关于那天的诗 但你一直没有写完
You've started a few poems about that day, but you never finished them.
我很抱歉 贝可
I'm so sorry, Beck.
但这一切都不重要 因为我有了第二个最重要的发现
But none of this matters because of my second and greatest discovery.
上午11点06分 我们在书店相遇的一个小时后
11:06 a.m., an hour after our encounter at the bookstore,
在一次讨论用草药蒸法 清洁阴道的好处的群聊中 你写道…
amidst a group text on the merits of vaginal detoxing, you wrote...
“哇 刚遇到了一个 真正会阅读的男人”
[Beck] Wow. Just met a human male who actually reads.
“大家注意”
Alert the media.
“也许我终于是时候 要跟适合我的人约会了？”
What if it's finally time for me to date someone good for me?
谢谢你让我知道我并不是疯了
[Joe] Thank you for letting me know
-I wasn't crazy after all. -[door unlocks]
不！
[Joe] No!
对 我记得你上次寄钱来时说过什么
Yes, I remember what you said when you sent money last.
对 我很感激
Yes, I'm grateful.
我一直在工作 没有更便宜的地方住了
[scoffs] I'm working constantly. There's no place cheaper to live.
我有 他基本上是提议让我跟他上床
I did. He basically offered to sleep with me.
不 我不能举报他 不能那样
No, I can't report him. That's not how it works.
我不担心 我看过足够多的爱情喜剧
[Joe] I'm not worried. I've seen enough romantic comedies
知道像我这样的家伙 总是会陷入这种窘境
to know guys like me are always getting in jams like this.
不是学校 是社会 社会不是这样混的
Not the school, the world. That's not how the world works.
我知道你帮了我多少 只是… 我处境很困难 妈妈
I know how much you helped me, it's just... It's hard here, Mom.
[sighs]
好吧 我会搞定的
Okay. I'll figure it out.
好了 我也爱你
All right. Love you, too.
再见 妈妈
Bye, Mom.
[crying]
没事的 贝可
[Joe] It's okay, Beck.
[cell phone ringing]
嗨 贝可
Hi, Becks.
嘿 贱人 你在哪？来玩吧！
Hey, bitch, where you at? Come play!
我不能去 今天是我最糟糕的一天
I can't. I just had the worst day.
-发生什么事了？ -贝可小甜心 不管什么事
-What happened? -Aw. Beckalicious, whatever it is,
没什么我们解决不了的 好吗？
there's nothing that we can't fix, okay?
-对 我们还有很多酒 -我的天 有打折！
Yes, us and copious amounts of alcohol.
-[Peach] Oh, my God. There's a sale! -[chuckles]
[sighs]
-你们爱我吗？ -当然爱了
-You guys love me? -[Peach] Of course.
-你怎么会说这种话呢？ -那好吧
-[Lynn] Why would you even say that? -[Beck] Okay, then.
到绿点见面吧
Meet me in Greenpoint.
听着 不如你过来吧？好吗？过来
Look, why don't you come here? Okay? Come here.
-我们在的地方其实很好玩 -不行
[Lynn] It's actually really fun where we are.
-我保证 -对
-No. -[Lynn] I promise.
我有些要为自己做的事
[Peach] Yeah.
There's something I need to do for myself.
我在路上给你们发短信
I'll text you on my way.
一会儿见
See you soon.
-再见！ -再见！
-Bye! -Bye!
该死！
[sighs] Fuck!
我想我们要去绿点了 贝可
[Joe] I guess we're going to Greenpoint, Beck.
[woman singing and playing guitar]
我从没去过绿点
I never go to Greenpoint.
但为爱会做傻事 对吗？
But the things you do for love, right?
嗨 好 我们再来几杯
[Beck] Hi. Um, okay, we're gonna get a few more drinks.
等等 等一下
Hold on, one second.
各位？
Guys?
她在想什么？
[Peach] What is she thinking?
开放麦克风是为模特兼歌手 兼歌曲作家兼素食主义者准备的
Open mics are for models-slash- singer-songwriters-slash-vegans.
这些人不想听
These people don't want to hear
某个想要成功的人 读什么关于凄惨生活的诗之类的
some wannabe read a poem about the bleakness of life or whatever.
你的朋友不靠谱 那个皮琪是最不靠谱的
[Joe] Your friends are disloyal. And that Peach is the worst.
[laughing]
再来一轮腌菜盐水酒
-[yells] Ooh. -Another round of picklebacks.
贝可宝贝 要挑今晚吗？
Beckish, do we think now's the night?
是的
Positive.
我最近的生活都是在挣扎求生
All of my life lately has been about surviving.
我需要提醒自己我最初来这里的原因
I need to remind myself why I came here in the first place.
-对 -对
-Yes. -Yeah.
-去吧 好耶 -你一直在给谁发短信？
-You go. So good. -Who do you keep texting?
我邀请了本吉
I invited Benji.
-贝可… -什么？他喜欢诗
-Beck... -What? He likes poetry.
-当然 -他发短信说他要来？
-For sure. -And he texted he was coming?
他差不多45分钟前 发了一串微笑的表情
He texted a row of smile emojis, like, 45 minutes ago.
有些男人就是混蛋 你得明白这点
Some guys are assholes, and you just have to realize that.
我知道 皮琪
I get it, Peach.
是你跟我说要一直提醒你 他是个王八蛋的
You're the one who told me to keep reminding you he's a bastard.
接下来有请吉娜薇贝可
Up next, we have Guinevere Beck.
Whoo!
-好了 -好了
-All right. -All right.
敬脆弱和欺骗！
To vulnerability and shit!
对
[Lynn] Yeah.
-干杯 -好的
-Cheers. -Okay.
-好的 -好的
-[Beck] Okay. -[Lynn] Okay.
好好表现 贝可！
[Annika] Kill it, Beck!
嗨 各位 我是贝可 我是个…
Hey, everyone. Um, I'm Beck, and I'm... [chuckles]
不想听上去好像 随便吧 但…
Not to sound like, you know, whatever, but just...
我是个诗人
I'm a poet.
对 你是！
Yeah, you are!
Whoo!
对 你是！
[Lynn] Yeah, you are!
“一天 你将不再需要爱
"One day, you won't need love anymore
一天 你将不再在这世界上行走
One day, you won't walk through the world
好像让一切停下是你的工作
As though it was your job To hold everything up
太阳 夜晚难过的部分
The sun, the hard part of the night
你被敲门声吵醒的秘密时光
The secret time when you wake To the sound of beating
你起身去开门 但他不在门口
Rise to answer the door But he's not there
因为那是你内心的声音
Because that sound is coming From inside you
你无法去应答 哪怕你进入内心深处
And you cannot answer it No matter how far in you go"
Whoo!
你就像脆弱的孩子 爱着帅气的霸凌者一样爱着他
"You loved him the way Fragile kids love gorgeous bullies
你写关于他的歌 你…” 我是说…
-You wrote songs about him. You..." -[cymbals crash]
Uh, I mean... [chuckles softly]
“你写关于他的诗
"You wrote poems about him
你还在写关于他的诗 你现在就在写一首”
You still write poems about him You're writing one right now"
你为什么这么难过？你太难过了
[man] Why're you so sad? You're just so sad.
换点高兴的东西可能会更好
Just something happier, for a change, might be nice.
我想大家都同意 换歌手回来唱歌吧
I think everyone agrees. Get the singer back.
抱歉 我只是…我忘记读到哪了
[stuttering] Sorry. I just... I lost my place.
我要花点时间看我读到哪了
It'll just take a second to find where I was.
我看不下去了 对不起 我就是不能
[Joe] I can't stand seeing this. I'm sorry. I just can't.
你是什么情况很明显 你被爱蒙蔽了双眼
It's obvious what you are. You're blind with love.
你爱的东西 写作、这个城市、你的朋友们
And what you love, writing, this city, your friends,
最重要的是 像本吉那样的男人
most of all, men like Benji,
所有这些的共同点就是 他们永远不会也爱你
what all those have in common is they will never love you back.
而你却付出所有
While you give everything.
我们都这么全力以赴 真疯狂 我们很像 贝可
It's crazy the lengths we go. We're a lot alike, Beck.
最后的真爱
Last of the true romantics.
机头 在纽约运输线上的
[homeless man] ♪ Engine Engine number nine ♪
九号机头…
♪ On the New York transit line... ♪
我正跟我的新朋友“无家可归的 疯子先生”思考这个问题时
[Joe] I was considering this with my new friend,
Mr. Bat-Shit Homeless Guy,
这周第二件最幸运的事发生了
when the second luckiest thing this week happened.
这是真的吗？
Could it really be?
感觉像是在做梦
It feels like I'm dreaming.
不是做梦
I'm not.
贝可 你太醉了 不能独自一人
Beck, you're too drunk to be alone.
要是有变态跟踪你到这里怎么办？
What if some sicko had followed you down here?
你太醉了 不能离轨道站得这么近
And you're too wasted to be standing so close to the tracks.
贝可！别再给那个自大的 卖苏打水、放你鸽子的混蛋发短信了
Beck! Beck, stop texting that arrogant club-soda, no-show dickhead.
（我读诗时你为什么不在？）
要是我的火车脱轨了
♪ If my train jump off the track ♪
你想要本吉
[Joe] You want Benji.
（我想要你过来的）
你需要本吉 你抓着那手机 好像它就是本吉一样
You need Benji. You hold that phone like it is Benji,
因为那是你唯一能跟他联系的方式
'cause it's your only means to stay connected.
忘了本吉吧
Forget Benji.
去他的手机吧
And to hell with that phone.
[gasps and grunts]
捡起来！
[homeless man] ♪ Pick it up! Pick it up! Pick it up... ♪
[coughing]
机头 在纽约运输线路上的
♪ Engine, engine number nine ♪
九号机头
♪ On the New York transit line... ♪
嘿！
Hey! Hey!
你还好吗？你没事吧？ 你能站起来吗？
You okay? Are you all right? Can you stand up?
别动
Just stay still.
碰一下那东西就会让你触电的 好了
Half that shit down there can electrocute you, all right,
把手给我
so just give me your hand.
捡起来！
[homeless man] ♪ Pick it up! Pick it up! ♪
♪ Pick it up! Pick it up... ♪
先生 拜托 别唱了！
Sir, please, shut up!
把手给我
Give me your hand.
地铁要来了
Train's coming.
捡起来！
♪ Pick it up! Pick it up! Pick it up! Pick it up! ♪
你的手！快！
Your hand! Now!
捡起来！
♪ Pick it up! ♪
[horn blaring]
[vomits]
Ugh.
我的天 太对不起了
-Oh, my God. Oh, my God. I am so sorry. -Whoo.
不 没关系
No, it's fine. It's fine.
我本来就讨厌…我讨厌这件外套
I, uh, hated... I hated this jacket. Ugh.
-真的很抱歉 -没事
-I really am sorry. -It's okay.
可以吗？
You mind?
当然
Sure, um...
我帮你叫辆出租车 好吗？
You know what? Let's get you in a cab. All right?
我并不总是这样的
I'm not always like this.
我猜你今晚不太顺心
I figured you had some kind of night.
算是吧
Some kind of.
嘿 我不想听上去 像个跟踪狂 但是…
Hey, I don't want to sound like a stalker, but...
我想我认识你
I think I know you.
那个…对 当然认识
Oh, the... Right. [chuckles] Of course.
我想起来了 真抱歉
I remember. I'm sorry.
这是我清醒时 把头发扎起来的样子
This is what I look like when I'm sober and have my hair up.
对 不 我记得
Yeah. No, I... I remember.
没事 我长着一张大众脸
It's okay, I have a pretty bland face.
不 不是的
No, you don't.
对 《绝望的人们》我记得
Yeah, uh, Desperate Characters. I remember.
对
Yeah.
你要去哪？
Where are you headed?
格林威治村 你顺路吗？
Village. You anywhere close?
跟我一起搭车吧 这是我起码能做的
Ride with me. It's the least I can do.
好的
Okay.
你来这里是想作出一番成就吗？ 我是的 但不行
Did you move here to be something? I did. But it's not working out.
我一天要连轴转18个小时 为什么？
And I'm just running around 18 hours a day. Why?
天啊！算了吧 对不起
Oh, God! Never mind. Sorry.
不 请别这样 我有时候也这么觉得
No, please. I feel the same way sometimes.
我认识个开书店的人
This guy I know, he owns the bookstore.
他有一次告诉我说 所有的书都证明了一个真理
He once told me that all books add up to one essential truth.
就是如果你的智商 超过了某一个数值…
Which is, if your IQ is above a certain number...
生活就非常难以忍受了 而且那个数值都不是很高
life is pretty much unbearable. And the number is not even that high.
我确实觉得如果我笨一点会更开心
[chuckles] I do think I'd be happier if I was stupider.
那世上的人就不会知道你写的诗了
[chuckles] But then the world wouldn't know your poetry.
你怎么知道我写诗？
How'd you know I write poetry?
哪个在纽约的年轻作家不写呢？
Doesn't every young writer in New York?
我读过很多诗歌
I mean, I read a lot of poetry.
你喜欢谁？
Who do you like?
斯特兰德、塞克斯顿、梅里尔…
Strand, Sexton, Merrill...
这些正是我放在床头柜上的
You're describing my nightstand.
如果你每晚都要读他们的诗入睡
[scoffs] Well, if you read them to get to sleep every night,
你绝对属于这里
then you definitely belong here.
-你姓什么来着？ -戈登伯格
-What was your last name again? -Goldberg.
你是哪里人 乔伊戈登伯格？
Where did you come from, Joe Goldberg?
我在这里长大的
I grew up here.
我离开过一阵子 去追一个女孩
I left for a little while. Chasing a girl.
-但你回来了？ -是的 我想念这里
-But you came back? -Yeah, I missed it.
我也不擅长追人
And I'm not a good chaser.
我也不
[sighs] Me neither.
[groans]
我到了
Oh, this is, uh... This is me.
Mmm-hmm. It's not bad.
不错啊
谢谢你让我清醒过来
Thank you for sobering me up.
还有谢谢你救了我
And for saving my life.
不 我没有救你
No, I didn't... I didn't save your life.
有 你救了我
Yeah, you did.
[knock on window]
天啊
Oh, God.
当然了
[Joe] Of course.
-是本吉 -嗨
-Benji. -[Beck] Hi.
这是乔伊 不夸张地说 他今晚救了我的命
Um, this is Joe. He literally saved my life tonight.
我跌倒掉到了铁轨上 太疯狂了
I... I fell on the tracks. It was crazy.
宝贝 我跟你说过这世上还是好人多
Babe, I told you people are basically good.
干得好 兄弟
It's a great job, bro.
“兄弟” 你这个长发男
[Joe] "Bro." You waste of hair.
好了 贝可 这里很冷
Okay. Beck, it's freezing out here.
-等等 也许你可以给我留个联系… -好
-Wait. Maybe I can get your info... -Yeah. Um...
该死！
Shit!
我的手机！
My phone!
我一定是把它落在地铁上了
-I must've dropped it in the subway. -Oh.
好吧 或者给我你的手机号也行
Uh, okay, well. Just maybe give me your number,
等你有新手机我们就能联系了
for when you get a replacement.
我主要是发邮件
I'm basically enslaved to e-mail.
我懂 聪明 我其实就是个陌生人 怎么小心都不为过
[Joe] I get it. Smart. I'm practically a stranger. Can't be too careful.
好的
Okay.
地址是“贝可的真实人生” 发到谷歌邮箱
It's BeckInRealLife@gmail.com
好的
-[typing] -All right.
“贝可的真实人生”
"Beck in real life."
谢谢
Thank you.
-这就是我这周了解到的 -抱歉我没赶到
[Joe] Here's what I learned this week.
[Benji] Sorry I didn't make it, you know?
你很特别 你有才华 你有激情
[Joe] You are special. You're talented. You're passionate.
你很聪明
You're smart.
只是在有些方面 你真的不聪明 像是你不锁手机
Except in the ways you are really not. Like not locking your phone.
还有爱上像本吉这种男人 你更清楚 但你停不下来
And falling for men like Benji. You know better, but you can't stop.
因为 每个人都需要另一个人
Because, well, because everyone needs someone.
你真正需要的是找个人拯救你
What you really need is someone to save you.
我能帮忙 贝可 让我帮你
I can help, Beck. Let me help you.
乔伊
[Paco] Joe.
帕克 嘿
Pac. Hey.
怎么了？你在这里干什么？
What's going on? What're you doing out here?
是罗恩
It's Ron.
他喝醉了回到家里
He came home drunk.
开始叫喊
He started yelling.
说我自以为很聪明
Saying I thought I was smart,
读我的书 把他看成一个笨蛋
reading my books and looking at him like he's dumb.
怎么了？他伤害你了吗？
What happened? Did he hurt you?
不 他没有碰我
No, he didn't touch me.
我努力想阻止他…
I tried to stop him...
-对不起 -帕克
-I'm sorry. -Paco.
帕克 没事 真的 没事的
Paco, it's okay. Really. It's okay.
跟我来吧 我们能处理好的 好吗？
You know what? Come with me. We can fix this together. All right?
解决问题的第一步
So, the first step to fixing something
就是要知道 不管破损看上去 有多严重 都是能补救好的
is to know no matter how destroyed it seems, it can always be saved.
书也不例外 你明白吗？
Books are no exception. You got it?
明白
Got it.
这有一台印机 其实就是个巨大的夹钳
So what we have here is a lying press. Basically just a huge clamp.
聚醋酸乙烯酯胶水
Polyvinyl-acetate glue,
意思是不会有酸烧坏书页 这里有针、线
means no acid to burn the pages. Got your needle, thread,
最后 还有兔八哥那里弄来的…
and finally, right out of Bugs Bunny...
可靠的锤子
a trusty mallet.
看到这个了吗？
You see this?
我们不需要这个
We don't need this.
乔诺！听听这个
[Benji] Johno! Listen to this.
“亲爱的本吉 我听说了你的汽水
"Dear Benji, heard about your soda.
有兴趣将你的产品 纳入秋季必须要尝试的清单中
Am interested in including you on my fall list of must-tries.
想跟你聊聊 也许试喝一下？ 杰夫佩文西”
Would love to discuss. Perhaps even try some? Jeff Pevensey."
是你一直在转发他推特的那个人吗？
That's the dude you're always retweeting?
他是《纽约》杂志的编辑
It's the culture guy from New York magazine.
回复他啊 兄弟
Hit him back, bro.
当然 我得想好怎么回复他 别烦我
No shit. Back off while I think.
杰夫 逗号 收到你的短信很高兴 兄弟 句号
Jeff, comma, so nice to hear from you, bud, period.
对 我们的汽水超赞 句号
Yeah, our sodas are legit, period.
我想跟你见面让你试喝一下 句号
I would love to meet up to have you try the goods, period.
让我们安排一下吧
Let's set something up.
顺着书脊小心地刮
Scrape carefully along the spine.
当然 你也要小心别刮到手指
Of course, you've got to watch your fingers.
[cell phone vibrates]
“听上去不错 我可以在会议的空档 给你电话看你有没有空”
"Sounds great. I can call between meetings to see if you're available."
这会让我们更上一层楼
This is gonna take us next level.
我们什么时候能见他？
What time do you think we'll meet?
无意冒犯 我们讨论过的
No offense, we discussed this.
在初期 产品还是让一个人 来介绍比较好
It's best if the product has one clear face at the beginning.
让我来更合适
That's just more me.
好 书脊缝好了
[Joe] Okay, the spine is sewn.
你拿着这个 尽可能拉紧 那边
So you take this, pull it as tight as you can, that way.
对 就是这样
Yeah. That's it.
杰夫！
Jeff!
胶水涂好了 我们装订好了
The glue is set. We've applied the binder.
现在…
Now...
你要很精准 力道也要恰到好处
you gotta be precise, and use exactly the force needed.
嘿！
Hey!
嘿 伙计 杰夫 很高兴见到你 伙计
Hey, man. Jeff. Nice to meet you, man.
我也很高兴见到你 你之前来过这里吗？
Nice to meet you, too. Have you been here before?
这是个…还没有很多人知道这里
It's a... Not a lot of people know about it yet.
这是个很棒的业余休闲的地方 非常隐蔽
It's an incredible after-hours. Very exclusive.
对 我来过几次
Yeah, I've been here a couple of times.
是吗？
-Yeah? -Hmm.
好极了
Oh. Well, good.
那你会觉得像在家里一样
So you'll feel right at home, then.
你先请
Please, after you.
好的
All right.
往下走就行了 向左拐
It's just down. To the left.
嘿 伙计 我在想也许…
Hey, man, I'm thinking maybe...
门被推开时是下午2点 我准备好了
[Joe] It's 2:00 p.m. when the door chimes, and I'm ready.
你跟你的女朋友们说你会过来 我知道 因为你的手机在我这里
You told your girlfriends you'd come by. I know this because I have your phone.
-我过会儿回来 -好的
-I'll be back. -[Joe] Okay.
嘿
Hey.
记得我吗？差点死在地铁铁轨上的？
Remember me? From almost dying on the train tracks? [chuckles]
我要想想 等等
Uh, it rings a bell. Hang on. Hang on.
我想对你说声谢谢
I wanted to say thank you.
不 你已经说过了
No. You already did that.
再次谢谢你
Well, uh, thanks again. [chuckles]
我很抱歉那晚匆匆就离开了
And I'm sorry for, uh, running off the other night.
-你有客人 -不算
-You had a guest. -Hardly.
我有礼物要送给你
So, I got you a present.
不 请别这样 你不用给我买任何东西
No, please. You don't have to get me anything.
别说了 看看吧
Shut up and just look at it.
“机头 纽约运输线路上的九号机头
"Engine, engine number nine On the New York transit line
如果你的女孩跌落在铁轨上 扶她起来”
If your girl falls on the track Pick her up, pick her up, pick her up"
我们已经有只有我们俩才懂的笑话了
[Joe] We already have in-jokes.
那么…
So...
总之 礼物你收到了 我最好…
anyway, that. And I better--
也许你要是不太忙的话 我们能找个时候喝一杯？
Maybe if you're not too busy, we could get a drink sometime?
当然可以
Sure.
但我还是没找到我的手机
Ugh. But I still can't find my phone.
我知道 发邮件吧
I know. E-mail.
没错
That's right.
再见 乔伊
See ya, Joe.
希望尽快看到你 贝可
See you soon, Beck.
干得漂亮 先生
Well played, sir.
干得漂亮
Well played.
我并不总是对的 我是人 会犯错
[Joe] I'm not always right. I'm human. I make mistakes.
你们会看到的
You'll see.
我得下楼去检查一批书
I have to check on a shipment downstairs.
-你能看着收银机吗？ -可以
-Can you watch the register? -Yeah.
见鬼 也许我就是个 坠入爱河的傻瓜…
[Joe] Hell, maybe I'm just a fool in love...
但我看你看得很准
but I'm right about you,
我要帮你过上 你应该过上的生活 贝可
and I'm going to help you get the life you deserve, Beck.
[Benji breathing heavily]
求你了
Please.
不管你觉得我做了什么事 你找错人了
Whatever you think I did, you got the wrong guy.
不
No.
我没有
I don't.
（谨以此片深切追念尼克格里芬）
字幕翻译： 葛晓丹